

CAREER VISION

Seeking a challenging, responsible and dynamic position in renowned organization where all my energies, knowledge and experience can be effectively utilized for benefit of the organization and enhancement of my career.

CONTACTS

- Lahore, Pakistan
- +92 324 7770106
- approvaltrick@gmail.com
- gejawad
- https://onfusion.github.io/

PERSONAL SKILLS

Communication	
Team Work	
Creativity	
Dedication	
Confidence	
Leadership	

Jawad Bhatti

Sr. Consultant Salesforce / Front-End / UI Developer

PROFILE

Creative Front-End Developer offering 9+ years of experience providing high-impact web solutions for diverse industry organizations. Over the past 9 years, as a Frontend Developer, I have designed, developed, and launched customized, highly responsive websites and e-commerce solutions using advanced technologies. In addition, I have consistently met client expectations and project milestones while working effectively in deadline-driven environments.

TECHNOLOGY & FRAMEWORK

- SFCC, SFRA, Demandware
- Material UI, Semantic UI
- Vue JS

- **Twitter Bootstrap**
- Angular JS, Angular
- React JS, Knockout JS

PROFESSIONAL SKILLS

- HTML/HTML5
- SASS/LESS, Compass
- Pug JS
- Node JS
- PHP, MySQL
- WordPress, Shopify
- Git, SVN, GitHub
- UI/UX Designin

- CSS/CSS3
- JavaScript, jQuery
- TypeScript
- C++
- Laravel
- Gulp, Grunt, Webpack
- NPM, Yarn, Composer
- Photoshop

WORK HISTORY

Systems Ltd.

Lahore

2021 - Present

Sr. Consultant Salesforce

Sr. Front-End Developer

Provide Salesforce Commerce Cloud (SFCC) technology expertise for solution design and technical implementation. Design, code, unit test, and code review iterative improvements to platform.

Worked closely with programmers and clients to meet

project requirements, goals, and desired functionality.

Developed and integrated customized themes into WordPress, Drupal, and PHP based web applications.

Zepto Systems PVT Ltd.

Islamabad

2015 - 2021

Faisalabad

2014 - 2015

Sitara InfoTech PVT Ltd. • Web Developer

Designed and maintained both corporate and client websites, using scripting languages and CMS including WordPress. Developed websites from front to backend using HTML/CSS, Bootstrap, and PHP.

EDUCATION

2021

Master's Degree

Virtual University of Pakistan

2009 - 2011

Bachelor

Punjab University of Lahore

2007 - 2009

Intermediate

P.B.T.E of Lahore, Pakistan

2006 - 2007

Matric

B.I.S.E Faisalabad, Pakistan

CERTIFICATION

2015

Web Development

EVS Learning Faisalabad, Pakistan.

2013

Web Designing

ApTech, Pakistan

2011

CCA (Course of computer application)

TEVETA - P.B.T.E Lahore, Pakistan

LANGUAGE

English

Urdu

Digital Solution PVT Ltd. Jr. Web Developer

Faisalabad 2013 - 2014

Collaborated with the UX/UI design teams to improve the website and applications, increasing conversion rates by 40%. Performed there for outsource projects based on WordPress CMS.

IT Empire PVT Ltd.

Faisalabad 2011 - 2013

Jr. Web Developer

Performed in this organization as Jr. developer, operate several websites based on B2Evolution, WordPress and Joomla CMS.

PROJECTS

KaDeWe

Salesforce (SFCC/SFRA), Node JS https://kadewe.de/

EBW

Salesforce (SFCC/SFRA), Node JS https://everythingbutwater.com/

Movein 4

PHP Zend Framework, Knockout JS https://poilet.mymovein.com/

QS Hub

Angular JS, Node JS, PHP https://qs-hub.qs.com/

QS - Quacquarelli Symonds

WordPress, JavaScript, PHP https://www.qs.com/

Top Universities

Drupal, JavaScript, SCSS, PHP https://www.topuniversities.com/

Top MBA

Drupal, JavaScript, SCSS, PHP https://www.topmba.com/

KTech Solutions Ltd.

WordPress, JavaScript, PHP http://www.ktechsol.com/

HOBBIES / INTEREST



Computing



Gaming



Photography



Travel



Music